{
    "subject": "Emilio_Fern\u00e1ndez",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "The_Torch__film_",
    "human_readable": "Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed the film The Torch.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9315885305404663,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.86159747838974,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8376778364181519,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Torch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6830993294715881,
            "question": "Was Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez known for directing any other famous films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43205851316452026,
            "question": "Who were some of the actors in 'The Torch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41041839122772217,
            "question": "What is Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez's legacy as a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3126176595687866,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'The Torch'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29148364067077637,
            "question": "What year was 'The Torch' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17115792632102966,
            "question": "What genre is 'The Torch' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.142396479845047,
            "question": "Are there any themes explored in 'The Torch' that are still relevant today?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed the film The Torch.",
            "html": "yago_9214_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is 'The Torch' likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_9214_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'The Torch' released?",
            "html": "yago_9214_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the plot of 'The Torch'?",
            "html": "yago_9214_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_9214_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_9214/re-ranker-msmarco/42.txt contains a section titled \"THE TORCH/ DEL ODIO NACE EL AMOR\" which explicitly states that it was directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"The Torch (Spanish: Del odio nace el amor, meaning \"love is born from hate\") is a 1950 Mexican/American film directed by Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez.\" This supports the statement that Emilio Fern\u00e1ndez directed the film The Torch."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}